- ♪ ♪
♪ ♪
- What do you think, boy?
你觉得呢，小伙子？
Best episode of Celebrity Dog Houses ever?
有史以来最好的一集《名人狗屋》？
[dog barks] Yeah.
（狗叫声）是啊。
- And with the newly added walk-in treat bin,
而且新增了步入式零食箱，
Beyonce's bichon, Bichonce, is one lucky single lady.
碧昂斯的比熊犬，比熊丝，真是个幸运的单身女士。
- Well, if you like it, you better put a leash on it.
好吧，如果你喜欢，你最好给它套上牵引绳。
[dog barks]
（狗叫声）
[sighs]
（叹气）
What do you say? We're good boys.
你说呢？我们是好孩子。
We deserve a treat.
我们值得奖励。
[spaghetti western music]
[意大利式西部片音乐]
♪ ♪
- Hands off! - You now hands off!
- 别碰！ - 现在别碰！
- That's not even real English! [all scream]
- 那根本不是真正的英语！[所有人尖叫]
- Wait, wait.
- 等等，等等。
Good boy, go get it! Mm.
好孩子，去拿吧！嗯。
And that, my furry friend, is how it's done.
而那，我的毛茸茸的朋友，就是怎么做成的。
- [overlapping arguing] - [sighs]
- [重叠争吵] - [叹气]
- We can't fight over the remote every time we want to watch TV.
- 我们不能每次想看电视都为遥控器打架。
- He's right. You should just let me have it.
- 他说得对。你应该直接让我拿。
- You all know your lies are better when I'm in control.
- 你们都知道，当我在掌控时，你们的谎言会更好。
- You mean when I'm in control.
- 你是说当我在掌控时。
- I'd like to be in control for once.
- 我想有一次能掌控。
- Please, leave this to the big dogs.
- 拜托，这种事交给大狗们处理。
- Yeah, and, Dicky, why are you still in this?
- 是啊，迪基，你为什么还在这儿？
You know Ricky or I always end up with it.
你知道要么是瑞奇，要么总是我拿到它。
- We wanna be big dogs. - Yeah.
- 我们也想做大狗。 - 对。
- Fine, the only fair way to do this
- 好吧，唯一公平的做法
is if we all let go at the same time.
是我们同时放手。
- Fine. - Fine.
- Woof.
- Okay. One, two, three.
- Ha! You let go.
The remote is mine.
Well, well, well, there's a new dog in the yard.
- Woof.
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- [whistling melody]
[rhythmic clapping] - ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
有节奏的拍手声 - ♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
- [whistling melody]
吹口哨的旋律
♪ ♪
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na-na ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐呐 ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na-na ♪
- ♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na, na, na ♪
♪ 一，二 ♪ - ♪ 呐，呐，呐 ♪
- ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
- ♪ ♪
♪ ♪
- You guys cheated! I'm not surprised about you.
你们作弊了！我对此并不惊讶。
You're the, "I can't stand to lose" girl.
你是那个'我不能忍受失败'的女孩。
But, Dicky, you're supposed to be
但是，Dicky，你应该是个
the cool, "I don't care" guy.
那个酷酷的'我不在乎'的家伙。
- Now I'm the cool, "I got the remote" guy.
- 现在我是那个酷酷的'我拿着遥控器'的家伙。
- Ooh, can I move up to, "I don't care" guy?
- 哦，我能升级成'我不在乎'的家伙吗？
- Real "I don't care" guys don't care enough
- 真正'我不在乎'的人连问这个问题都不在乎。
to ask that question.
- 那不是真的。我的意思是，随便啦。
- That's not true. I mean, whatevs.
- 面对现实吧，你更像那个'我们不用担心'的家伙。
- Face it, you're more like the, "Guy we don't have to worry about" guy.
- [轻笑] Dicky，这挺可爱的，而且骗过Ricky值得表扬，
- [chuckles] Dicky, this was cute, and props for tricking Ricky,
但我想我们俩都知道这会怎么结束——
but I think we both know how this is gonna end--
You wishing it never began, so step down.
你希望它从未开始，所以退下吧。
- Oh, I'll step down.
哦，我会退下的。
[grunts] - Ow!
哎哟！
Oh, you want to dance? Let's dance!
哦，你想跳舞？来跳舞吧！
- Ow, ow.
哎哟，哎哟。
- I'm not letting go. - Neither am I.
我不会放手的。
[buzzer]
我也不会。
- You just deleted Dad's show!
你刚刚删除了爸爸的节目！
I mean, whatevs.
我是说，随便啦。
- Celebrity Dog Houses!
《名人狗屋》！
That was the season fur-nale. [gasps]
那是季终集。[吸气声]
What have you done?
你做了什么？
- I didn't do anything.
- 我什么都没做。
- Why is it whenever I leave the room,
- 为什么每次我离开房间，
you kids fight over the remote?
你们这些孩子就抢遥控器？
- Because you don't like it when we do it in front of you.
- 因为你不喜欢我们在你面前这样做。
- And because they don't have any remote skills. - Please, I've got the skills to pay the bills.
- 而且因为他们没有遥控技能。 - 拜托，我有付账单的技能。
- [sighs] There is only one person who pays the bills around here,
- [叹气] 这里只有一个人付账单，
and that is your mother.
那就是你们的妈妈。
Now, that's it.
现在，就这样了。
No more television for the whole weekend.
整个周末都不能看电视了。
Both: What?
什么？
- Good parenting, Dad. They deserve it.
- 爸爸，这是良好的教育方式。他们是自找的。
- All of you. Both: What?
- 你们所有人。什么？
- I don't want any fighting this weekend.
- 这个周末我不希望有任何争吵。
Tomorrow is your mother and my anniversary.
明天是你妈妈和我的结婚纪念日。
And this year, you are not gonna ruin it.
今年，你们不会搞砸它的。
- But we didn't ruin it last year.
- 但我们去年没搞砸啊。
You did.
是你搞砸的。
- Yeah, you're the one who bought your lady
- 是的，是你给你的女士
those snow tires.
买了那些雪地轮胎。
- Well, this year is gonna be perfect,
- 好吧，今年一定会很完美，
especially now that I don't have to listen to you guys
特别是现在我不用再听你们
argue about who's the best at the remote,
争论谁遥控器玩得最好，
which, by the way, is pointless since we all know it's me.
顺便说一句，这毫无意义，因为我们大家都知道是我。
You might want to film this.
你可能想把这个录下来。
Go. Stop.
开始。停。
- You didn't do anything.
- 你什么都没做。
- Check the footage, Spielberg, in slo-mo.
- 斯皮尔伯格，慢动作回放看看。
All: Ooh.
哦。
- Well, at least we can still watch TV on this all day.
至少我们还可以整天用这个看电视。
- Looking for this?
在找这个吗？
Oh. Oh, I look good on camera.
哦。哦，我在镜头前看起来不错。
- [whistling melody]
[吹口哨旋律]
- I know it's a day early, but I really wanted to give you your anniversary present.
我知道提前了一天，但我真的很想给你周年礼物。
Just three more feet. - Ow!
再走三英尺。 - 哎哟！
- Oh, sorry.
哦，对不起。
I always forget how big your feet are.
我总是忘记你的脚有多大。
- [scoffs] - Ow.
[嗤之以鼻] - 哎哟。
Ta-da! You can look now.
塔-达！你现在可以看了。
- Yeah, but then I'll see the rake or the box of yarn
- 是的，但那样我就会看到耙子或那盒毛线
or the gutters, and I'll have to pretend like I love it.
或者排水沟，我就得假装我很喜欢。
[gasps] I love it!
[吸气] 我喜欢！
- There is no pleasing you. - [laughs]
- 你真是难以取悦。 - [笑]
No, this time I'm telling you the truth.
不，这次我说的实话。
You got me a new bed! - Wow, I finally did it?
你给我买了张新床！ - 哇，我终于做到了？
- You really did. - Ha!
- 你真的做到了。 - 哈！
Anne Harper, meet the Slumbertron,
安妮·哈珀，来见见Slumbertron，
the most technologically advanced sleep surface
地球上最先进的睡眠表面
on the planet.
在地球上。
It does everything. It, uh, adjusts...
它能做一切。它，呃，调节...
- [gasps]
－[吸气声]
- Heats... - Ooh.
－加热...－哦。
- Cools... - Ahh.
－冷却...－啊。
- Massages. - [laughs]
－按摩。－[笑声]
I love you.
我爱你。
- It also makes soothing sounds and has a humidifier.
－它还能播放舒缓的声音并带有加湿器。
- Hon, thank you so much.
－亲爱的，非常感谢你。
- Yeah, yeah, I'm awesome. What'd you get me?
－是啊，是啊，我真棒。你给我买了什么？
- Okay, well, I was gonna wait 'til tomorrow, but...
好吧，其实我本想明天再给你的，但是...
Here. - It's a universal remote!
给你的。
- Top of the line.
是个万能遥控器！
You are now the king of this castle with the power
顶级的。
to control all of the electrical appliances in the house.
你现在成了这个家的王者，拥有控制家里所有电器的力量。
Go ahead, say hello.
来吧，打个招呼。
- Hello? [angelic music]
你好？[天使般的音乐]
- Hello, Thomas. Ready to program.
你好，托马斯。准备编程。
Slumbertron programmed. - She's so fast.
斯伦勃特伦已编程。
I am gonna take you downstairs and introduce you to the TV.
她真快。我这就带你下楼去见见电视机。
Yes, I am. Yes, I am.
是的，我是。是的，我是。
- Tom, the whole "talking to the remote" thing is kinda weird.
汤姆，整个'对着遥控器说话'的事情有点奇怪。
I'll see you tonight, Mattress McConaughey.
今晚见，床垫麦康纳。
All right, all right, all right.
好吧，好吧，好吧。
- I wonder what's going on in there right now.
我想知道现在里面发生了什么。
- So many wonderful things.
有这么多美妙的事情。
- Thanks to you two cheaters, the only thing I can see
多亏了你们两个作弊者，我唯一能看到的就是你们作弊的脸。
is the reflection of your cheating faces.
我看过一部电影，里面有个孩子盯着电视非常用力，最后电视终于开了。
- I saw this movie once where this kid
然后他的头爆炸了。
stared at the TV super hard, and it finally came on.
我愿意冒这个险。
Then his head exploded.
然后他的头爆炸了。
- I'll take that chance. All: Me too.
我愿意冒这个险。所有人：我也是。
[all grunt]
[所有人用力哼声]
[all scream]
[所有人尖叫]
- Television programmed.
电视节目设置完成。
- What is that?
那是什么？
- Not what--who?
不是什么...是谁？
Dawn, Nicky, Ricky, Dicky, meet Clicky.
道恩，尼基，里奇，迪基，这是点击。
She's like a fifth child to me,
她就像我的第五个孩子，
except this one will actually do what I say.
只不过这个会听我的话。
- It's your Dad's new universal remote.
- 这是你爸爸的新万能遥控器。
- When I'm finished programming her,
- 等我编程完成后，
she'll control everything in the house.
她将控制家里的一切。
- That's sick, Dad!
- 太酷了，爸爸！
Show us how she turns on the TV again.
再给我们演示一下她怎么开电视。
- Oh, it's so easy. You--hey, nice try.
- 哦，非常简单。你——嘿，不错，试试看。
You're still not allowed to watch TV.
你还是不能看电视。
- Why not?
- 为什么不行？
- They were fighting over the remote,
- 他们在抢遥控器，
so I banned TV for the weekend.
所以我周末禁止看电视。
- Why would you do that? - I was parenting.
- 你为什么要这么做？ - 我在履行父母的职责。
- Tom, our anniversary is the one day a year
- 汤姆，我们的结婚纪念日是一年中的
we get to sleep in.
- 唯一一天我们可以睡个懒觉。
Let them have the TV just for tomorrow morning.
- 就让他们明天早上看会儿电视吧。
- But, if I go back on a punishment,
- 但如果我撤销惩罚，
isn't that bad parenting?
- 那不是糟糕的父母行为吗？
- [whispers]
- [低声说]
- All right, you kids can watch TV tomorrow morning.
- 好吧，孩子们明天早上可以看电视。
All: Yes!
- 所有人：太好了！
- But you have to share nicely and quietly,
- 但你们必须安静地分享，
and under no circumstances
而且在任何情况下
are you to disturb us before 10:00 a.m.
你们不得在上午10:00之前打扰我们
- [whispers] - [laughs]
- [低语] - [笑]
11:00 a.m.
上午11:00
- We won't. - Don't worry.
- 我们不会的。 - 别担心。
- Thank you. - Promise. - And if I have to come down here and break up a fight,
- 谢谢你。 - 我保证。 - 如果我不得不下楼来制止一场争吵，
whoever's responsible will lose TV for a month.
责任人将一个月不能看电视。
[ominous music]
[不祥的音乐]
- She even has comedic timing.
- 她甚至有喜剧时机感。
- This is awesome. - We're getting our lives back.
- 这太棒了。 - 我们正在找回我们的生活。
- All right, we've got a second chance here.
So no fighting over the remote and no waking up early
to try to steal it.
Can I trust you two this time? - Absolutely.
- No fighting over the remote.
- ♪ ♪
- I'm getting the remote first! - It's mine.
- You don't deserve the remote. - You can't even rewind.
- You scroll too slowly. - Your brain scrolls too slowly.
- Oh, hey, I think it's in this pillow.
Take a look.
看一下。
- Quiet down, you're gonna wake up Mom and Dad.
- 小声点，你会吵醒爸爸妈妈的。
- Where's the remote? - We don't know!
- 遥控器呢？ - 我们不知道！
- Dad must have forgot to put it out.
- 爸爸肯定是忘了拿出来了。
- Great, we get the remote back for the whole morning,
- 太好了，我们一早上都拿回了遥控器，
and now we can't even watch.
现在却看不了。
- Maybe the remote's in Mom and Dad's room.
- 也许遥控器在爸妈的房间里。
- I'm on it.
- 我去搞定。
- Stop! Stop, stop!
- 停！停，停！
We're not supposed to bother them under any circumstances.
无论如何我们都不应该打扰他们。
- Don't worry. They'll never know I'm there.
别担心。他们永远不会知道我在那里。
I'm like a super quiet ninja.
我就像一个超级安静的忍者。
Wa-ta!
哇-塔！
- I'm quieter than you!
我比你更安静！
- We gotta stop them.
我们必须阻止他们。
- Or do we?
还是我们？
- You found it. Hey, guys!
你找到了。嘿，伙计们！
- Shh.
嘘。
Let them wake up Mom and Dad.
让他们吵醒妈妈和爸爸。
- What are you doing?
你在做什么？
This is so unlike you.
这可不像你。
- Sometimes in order to win,
有时候，为了赢，
you have to do the opposite of what people expect.
你得反着人们的期望去做。
They think you're gonna zig, you gotta zag.
他们以为你要这么走，你就得那么走。
- It just feels weird.
只是感觉怪怪的。
You're the "I always do the right thing" guy.
你是那种‘总是做正确的事’的人。
- Did Dawn and Dicky do the right thing
当道恩和迪基骗我们的时候，他们做的是正确的事吗？
when they tricked us?
不是。
- No. - And how about when they got the TV taken away from us?
那他们让我们没了电视的时候呢？
- No.
也不是。
- So, when they wake up Mom and Dad, they'll lose TV,
- 所以，当他们吵醒爸爸妈妈时，他们会失去电视，
and you and I will have control
而你和我将掌控遥控器整整一个月！
over the remote for a whole month!
- 你在卖梦想，而我正在购买。
- You're selling dreams, and I'm buying.
♪ ♪
- [低语] 不在这里。我哪儿都看不到遥控器。
- [whispers] It's not here. I don't see the remote anywhere.
- 我也是。
- Me neither.
- [咕哝]
- [grunts]
[天使般的音乐]
[angelic music]
两人：咔哒。
Both: Clicky.
- 别碰它。咔哒是我的。
- Don't touch it. Clicky is mine.
- 别碰它。Clicky是我的。
- Stop! - Ow! Let go.
- 停！- 哎哟！放手。
- You hear that?
- 你听到了吗？
That's the sweet sound of Mom and Dad about to punish somebody.
- 那是爸妈即将惩罚某人的甜美声音。
- But not us. - Ow. Come on. Stop!
- 但不是我们。- 哎。快点。停！
- Happy anniver...sary.
- 快乐纪念...日。
- Where's Mom and Dad? - You didn't wake them up and get in trouble?
- 爸妈呢？- 你没吵醒他们惹麻烦吧？
- Nope. - Yay.
- 没有。- 耶。
- Is that Clicky?
- 那是Clicky吗？
- Yep, we couldn't find the TV remote.
- 是的，我们找不到电视遥控器。
- Don't worry, I'll have this baby back in Dad's hands
别担心，我会在爸爸醒来之前把这玩意儿放回去。
before he wakes up.
伙计们，这真的很糟糕。
- G-guys, this is really bad. - Nicky, scone check.
尼基，检查烤饼。
We don't want the bottoms to brown.
我们可不想底部烤焦了。
What--what did I tell you about zagging?
我跟你们说过拐弯走的事吗？
If they get caught with Clicky,
如果他们带着‘咔哒’被抓住了，
we could be in control of the TV forever.
我们可能永远控制着电视了。
- That's a lot of TV.
那可要看很多电视了。
- You are not Clicky-worthy.
你还不够资格用‘咔哒’。
- Please, you saw the way she lit up when she saw me.
求你们了，你们看到她见到我时有多兴奋了吗？
Both: What did you do?
你们做了什么？
- [chuckles]
- [轻笑]
It'll be fine. It's just some juice.
没事的，只是一些果汁。
[electricity crackles]
[电流噼啪声]
- Clicky: Television progr-- [voice distorts]
- 克利奇：电视节目——[声音失真]
- And some yogurt.
- 还有些酸奶。
- [laughs evilly]
- [邪恶地笑]
- Okay, I think she's dry. You ready?
- 好了，我想她干了。准备好了吗？
- Hold on.
- 等等。
I'm good.
我准备好了。
[muffled angelic noise]
[模糊的天使般的声音]
- Is it working?
- 它起作用了吗？
- Kinda, sorta, maybe. Here, let's try it on the TV.
- 有点，算是，可能吧。来，我们在电视上试试。
Please, please, please, please,
请，请，请，请，
please, please, please, please, please.
请，请，请，请，请。
- Maybe you didn't say "please" enough.
- 也许你说的“请”还不够多。
- That's weird. I pressed the TV button,
- 这很奇怪。我按了电视按钮，
but it made the lights go on and off.
但它让灯闪烁了。
- Maybe the lights button will make the TV come on.
- 也许灯光按钮会让电视打开。
[air blowing]
[风吹声]
That's the air conditioning. Give me that!
那是空调。给我那个！
See? Let a master do it.
看到了吗？让大师来操作。
[whirring]
[嗡嗡声]
- Way to go, master.
干得好，大师。
- Hey, if this were on TV, you would go,
嘿，如果这在电视上，你会说，
"Wow, I can't believe this is on TV."
“哇，我真不敢相信这会在电视上。”
- Great, now it's not doing anything.
太好了，现在它什么都没做。
- [groans]
[呻吟]
Tom, did you turn the bed heater on?
汤姆，你打开床加热器了吗？
- I thought you did. - Mm-mm.
我以为是你开的。 - 嗯，不是。
[both shouting]
- Oh, my God.
哦，我的天。
- Aah!
啊！
- Clicky, what happened to you?
Clicky，你怎么了？
[both gasp] - No, what?
不，什么？
[both screaming]
Tom, what's happening?
Tom，发生什么事了？
- The bed turned Clicky into a sandwich,
床把Clicky变成了三明治，
and now it's trying to turn us into one.
现在它正试图把我们变成一个。
We're the meat in a bed sandwich!
我们是床三明治里的肉！
Happy anniversary. - Oh, you too, sweetie.
周年快乐。 - 哦，你也是，亲爱的。
Aah!
啊！
- Well, that's the humidifier.
- 那是加湿器。
Works great, huh?
效果不错，是吧？
- See? Nothing.
- 看？什么都没有。
- Anne: [groans]
- 安妮：[呻吟]
- Maybe we need to press harder.
- 也许我们需要按得更用力。
[whales calling] - What is that noise?
[鲸鱼叫声] - 那是什么声音？
- Soothing whale sounds.
- 舒缓的鲸鱼声音。
- Not soothing! [drilling]
- 不舒缓！[钻孔声]
- Yo, Joey, I need that steel over here.
乔伊，我这边需要那块钢材。
- Why would they even put those sounds in there?
他们为什么要在那里放那些声音？
[sounds stop]
声音停止了。
[both sigh]
两人叹气。
- Oh, thank goodness.
哦，谢天谢地。
[both scream]
两人尖叫。
- Here we go again. - We need the kids!
又来了。我们需要孩子们！
[both scream]
两人尖叫。
- Okay. New plan.
好吧。新计划。
Here's what we do.
我们这么做。
We sneak Clicky back into Dad's hands.
我们悄悄把Clicky放回爸爸手里。
- Yeah, go on.
- 对，继续。
- That's it. That's all we do.
- 就是这样。我们就这么做。
- Oh. - You sound disappointed.
- 哦。 - 你听起来很失望。
- Well, it sounded like there was gonna be more.
- 嗯，听起来好像会有更多步骤。
I mean, I could have come up with that.
我的意思是，我本可以想到这个办法。
- But you didn't.
- 但你没有。
- You guys remotely closer to getting that thing fixed?
- 你们有没有更接近修好那东西？
Oh, I am on fuego today.
哦，我今天状态火热。
- Hold up there, lumpy butt.
- 等等，笨拙的屁股。
- It's not me, it's these blousy pants.
- 不是我，是这些宽松的裤子。
- You had this the whole time?
- 你一直都有这个？
- What? I thought I put that in the drawer.
- 什么？我以为我把它放抽屉里了。
I mean, not that I ever had it to put in the drawer.
我是说，并不是说我曾经拥有它并放进抽屉。
I mean, hey. You found the remote.
我是说，嘿。你找到了遥控器。
Let's go watch stuff, yay!
我们去看点东西吧，耶！
- You hid the remote.
- 是你藏了遥控器。
You wanted us to wake up Mom and Dad.
你想让我们叫醒爸爸妈妈。
- Quiet. Do you hear that?
- 安静。你听到了吗？
[distant screams]
[远处尖叫声]
It sounds like Mom and Dad are calling for us.
听起来像是爸爸妈妈在叫我们。
- Maybe they need help.
- 也许他们需要帮助。
- Please, we're not falling for another one of your tricks.
- 拜托，我们不会再上你的当。
- Why aren't they coming to help us?
- 他们为什么不自己来帮我们？
- We did tell them not to disturb us.
- 我们确实告诉过他们不要打扰我们。
- Why is this the first time they actually do what we say?
- 为什么这是他们第一次真正听我们的话？
- Honey, my foot itches. - Hold on.
- 亲爱的，我的脚痒。 - 稍等。
[groans]
[呻吟]
- [sighs]
- [叹气]
Thank you. - You're welcome.
谢谢。 - 不客气。
- Maybe Dad noticed Clicky is gone.
- 可能爸爸注意到Clicky不见了。
- What are you doing?
- 你在干什么？
- I'm going to tell them we didn't break Clicky.
- 我要告诉他们我们没有弄坏Clicky。
You know they're gonna believe whoever gets there first.
你知道他们会相信第一个到那里的人。
- Wow.
- 哇。
Nice job tricking them into going upstairs.
干得好，骗他们上楼。
- I wasn't tricking them!
- 我没有骗他们！
I'm freaking out!
我快吓死了！
You should be too.
你也应该这样。
- Me?
- 我？
- What if they tell Mom and Dad this was your fault?
- 如果他们告诉爸爸妈妈这是你的错怎么办？
- My fault--they're the ones who broke Clicky.
- 我的错——是他们弄坏了Clicky。
- Yeah, but you hid the TV remote
- 是啊，但你藏了电视遥控器
and started this whole thing!
还引发了这一切！
- I just wanted to watch TV.
- 我只是想看电视。
Wait! Don't listen to them!
等等！别听他们的！
- Help. - Please.
- 救命。 - 请。
- Dad, Dicky broke Clicky. - No, I didn't, she did.
- 爸爸，Dicky弄坏了Clicky。 - 不，我没有，是她弄的。
- Well, he's holding it. - Uh, no, I'm not.
- 嗯，他拿着它。 - 呃，不，我没有。
- Well, now, he's throwing it.
- 现在，他在扔它。
Hey, what happened to the bed?
嘿，床怎么了？
- Clicky's broken? - Get us out of here.
- 点击器坏了？ - 把我们弄出去。
We're stuck.
我们被困住了。
- But first, tell me what happened to Clicky.
- 但首先，告诉我点击器怎么了。
- No, first you will open this bed.
- 不，你先打开这张床。
- They're lying!
- 他们在撒谎！
I don't know how the remote got into my pocket.
我不知道遥控器怎么跑到我口袋里的。
Hey, what happened to the bed?
嘿，床怎么了？
- Just open it!
- 快打开！
[both sighing]
[两人叹气]
- What did you do to poor Clicky?
你对可怜的Clicky做了什么？
- It's all Ricky's fault! - You dropped it in yogurt.
都是Ricky的错！- 你把它掉进了酸奶里。
- [shouts] Yogurt?
- [喊叫] 酸奶？
I warned you. Ricky, Dicky, Dawn?
我警告过你们。Ricky, Dicky, Dawn？
No TV for a whole month. - Good parenting, Dad.
一个月不准看电视。- 好样的，爸爸。
Did these rude children wake you on your anniversary?
这些没礼貌的孩子在你们的纪念日吵醒你了吗？
For shame.
真丢人。
- What are you talking about? You knew about all this.
- 你在说什么？你早就知道这一切。
- Me?
- 我？
I've been so hard at work making breakfast.
我一直忙于做早餐，几乎没有注意到你们孩子气的争吵。
I hardly paid any attention to your childish arguing.
我几乎没注意到你们幼稚的争吵。
Scones?
司康饼？
- Thank you, Nicky.
谢谢你，尼基。
It's nice to know that at least one of our children
很高兴知道至少有一个孩子
cares more about us than about television.
比电视更关心我们。
- Well, after all you've given me, it's the least I could do.
嗯，毕竟你们给了我这么多，这是我至少能做的。
Oh. I forgot to butter the scones.
哦，我忘了给司康饼涂黄油了。
- Hold up there, butter boy. What are you up to?
等等，黄油小子，你在搞什么鬼？
- I'm starting to worry about you.
我开始担心你了。
- You should be worried.
你应该担心。
You've all underestimated me for too long.
你们所有人都太久地低估了我。
And now the chickens have come home to roost.
现在，报应来了。
- When did we get chickens?
- 我们什么时候养鸡了？
- There are no chickens.
- 没有鸡。
But there is a rat.
但有一只老鼠。
- You never let me use the remote, and now it's all mine.
- 你从不让我用遥控器，现在它是我的了。
- You were supposed to zig. - But I zagged.
- 你应该向左转。 - 但我向右转了。
- Nicky, I think those scones have been buttered enough-- with lies.
- 尼基，我觉得那些司康饼已经被谎言抹得够多了。
You see, not only is Clicky the child who listens to me,
你看，Clicky不仅是听我话的孩子，
she's also the one who tells me the truth.
她也是告诉我真相的那个孩子。
- Thank you.
谢谢。
- There's a logical explanation for this.
这有一个合乎逻辑的解释。
It was all his plan! He was the zag master.
这都是他的计划！他是那个变卦大师。
- Seriously? [overlapping arguing]
真的吗？
- Happy anniversary, honey.
周年快乐，亲爱的。
- Yeah, yeah.
是啊，是啊。
[arguing continues]
争吵继续。
- We probably should've just shared.
我们或许本该分享的。
- Yep.
对。
- Would have been better than this.
这会比现在好。
- This is going to be the longest month ever.
- 这将是史上最长的一个月。
- This is gonna be the best month ever.
- 这将是史上最好的一个月。
[both sigh]
[两人叹气]
[beeping]
[哔哔声]
- Oh! No, no, no! - No, no, no, no, no!
- 哦！不，不，不！- 不，不，不，不，不！
No, no, no! No, no, no, no, no!
不，不，不！不，不，不，不，不！
♪ ♪
[whistling melody]
[吹口哨旋律]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
- ♪ 耶！ ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪
- [cheerful melody]
[欢快的旋律]
- ♪
♪